# **Brandon Crawford**

## E-Commerce Major

Little Rock, AR 72202 (501)-413-0353 brcrawford@ualr.edu

#### **ABOUT**

Diligent E-Commerce major with a diverse background ready to start a career within the IT field. Experience with sales, windows based software, team/project management, website creation, optimization, and upkeep. Recently worked as Team Lead while creating a website for a local non-profit. Proficient with a wide range of programming languages and in touch with the rapidly evolving world of technology. Well traveled and well spoken with great people skills.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

South On Main, Little Rock AR - Server/Bartender

SEPTEMBER 2018 - PRESENT

- Cross trained as a server and bartender.
- Fine-dining with weekly shows and a wide range of clientele.

#### Flyway Brewing - Bartender

AUGUST 2017- DECEMBER 2018

- Face to face interactions with patrons in a fast paced environment.
- Employees worked as bartenders and waiters to entire taproom.

#### Dizzy's Bistro - Server

FEBRUARY 2015- AUGUST 2017

- Highest average sales.
- Help with creation of new food and beverage specials.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **UNIVERSITY OF ARKANSAS LITTLE ROCK** - B.S. in E-Commerce

AUGUST 2018 - MAY 2020

GPA: 3.50 - Dean's List and Chancellor's List

#### PULASKI TECHNICAL COLLEGE - A.S. in General Technology

AUGUST 2014- MAY 2016

GPA: 3.40

### IT SKILLS AND EXPERIENCE

- Google Analytics Certified
- Website creation for a non-profit organization
- Website optimization and upkeep for local business
- HTML5 & CSS3
- JavaScript
- PHP: MySQL
- Bootstrap
- Wordpress